Let's have a quick look at the NBC reporter search.
So we set up a search can be found under billed folder built in to search and inside the report as such,
we can find all the commands which we executed in the earlier sessions, the HMO, which will display
the entire set of commands and the lengths the lengths function which will help us to select the lunch
menu.
And then all the grep functions should be here.
So here we have all the grep functions, g grep, go, grep, jackrabbit grep, see grep and all those
things which we have executed earlier.
And here we have the go directory, refresh mode or mode path mode.
So everything is defined here.
So if you are interested, you can have a detailed look into the setup asset and see how that is implemented.